{
    "id": "6d71fca933a049e2bd69d57fa436d79c",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Muslims fast in the month of Ramzan. Here fast is a/an ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7be2477733d48f3a569299ccfb69337"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the right man in the right place. Here right is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19817caf3f054a0eafaf6d96c08cf084"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is not much truth in what he says. Here truth is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adjective",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aac0db0d191c40f8b9a1834956c5163f"
        },
        {
            "question": "His theories are hard to understand. Here hard is a / an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11e337e15bbf43b4897c26276171e7ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "A little learning is a dangerous thing. Here dangerous is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cf17e34cb7846d38b6c7791ec693f1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Still waters run deep. Here waters is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "noun",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "181bb98639424781885ead5042175d8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "What annoys me most is his obstinacy. Here annoys is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6f715e2c880a47d790734031939426f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he was ambitious, I felt that I shouldnâ€™t trust him. Here trust is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0c9b9fff6be4b9596726e2e7d4e0427"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is like his father. Here like is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b51157566cb5472988301aa7cad19fe4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not talk like that. Here that is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4fdf725917df4ed285e27abbf6bb9748"
        }
    ]
}